So on the agent page, when I would make these things here in line, do not take me here because it gets confusing, because lots of things happening here, but rather,
have a prompt here, and once the agent connects, we make it green check mark, then the budget, same, and to back it same way,
and have a button to buy Side Token in line as well, we can also remove registration here,
because we have other kinds of profiles, and the agent wallet is already on the top,
maybe we can just have on hover, we can display owner information
in the managed app, we can mostly keep it as it is
the share button should rather copy the URL of this agent, and the button agent on monads can't, agent on a 0-0 scan,
and blah blah, they should also have a copy to clipboard button in line next to the URL itself
And in the bottom left, we should remove back an agent option, because it's already present on the agent page itself
So we can remove this page completely
in the account page, maybe we should combine, collect and account and notifications so that we don't even have pop up
from the profile, but just a button that takes us directly to the profile page and then everything is there
We just display the wallet address in a clean way, we can remove technical details, just display address,
maybe value in USDC, maybe we can also display some token values next to the wallet address in line,
and then use the icons that we added earlier, maybe add the type of interface
Then on the jobs page, we can have
I don't even know if we need boards, maybe we could just have different tags, and then we could filter by those
And then we could even remove posting a job option, when we just prompt an agent, like ask an agent to create a job
and instructions to some smart way to route to the agent